Okay, so here we are in
好的，现在我们来到
the final of the Solution Videos
挑战自适应布局
for the Adeptly Adaptive Challenge,
系列的最后部分
and there are two things we need to accomplish here.
这有两个事情需要我们去完成
Each news item should be 200 X 275 in narrow state,
每一个新的元素在窄状态时，宽高为200*275
and 400 X 400 tall when in a wide state.
同时在宽状态时，宽高为400*400
And here we're defining the wide state
这里给我们宽状态的定义是
as 900 min window width.
窗口宽度大于等于900px
In the narrow state, the Headline should be 18 point,
在窄状态，这标题应当是18pt
and 26 point in the wide state.
在宽状态应该是26pt
And then also we're going to hide the AutoSuggestBox
同时我们还要在宽度小于等于400px的压缩状态下
when in a narrow state of 400 or less.
隐藏自动提示框
Okay, so this will apply really
好，这个效果仅
only to the MainPage.xaml.
用于MainPage.xaml
This will only apply to our User Control that we created The NewsItemControl..
这个仅用于我们创造的用户控制 NewsItemControl.
So let's go ahead and get started here,
然后我们从这里开始
and let's open up the NewsItemControl.
打开 NewsItemControl
And inside of our Grid,
在我们的Grid布局中
right after the Grid.RowDefinitions, we're going to
在Grid.RowDefinitions下面，我们要
start adding a VisualStateManager,
开始添加一个视觉状态管理器
creating the VisualState groups,
创建视觉状态组
and we'll create one VisualState group.
我们要创建一个视觉状态组
And inside that we'll create two VisualStates.
在这里我们要创建两个视觉状态
The first one I'm going to call the NarrowLayout,
第一个我们叫做窄布局
(typing on keyboard)
(打字中……)
and then the second one
然后是第二个
I'll call WideLayout.
我叫他宽布局
Not that it really matters,
其他它并不重要
because we're not referencing it by name.
因为我们不会通过名字来引用它
But any rate, okay,
不管怎样，好了
and then, here we go, VisualState.StateTriggers,
然后，这里添加，VisualState.StateTriggers
and then VisualState.Setters.
然后是 VisualState.Setters
and I'll just copy and paste that here as well.
我再复制再粘贴一下
All right, so in the Triggers, I'm going to
在这个触发器中，我将要
create an AdaptiveTrigger where
创建一个 AdaptiveTrigger
the MinWindowWidth
设置窄布局的最小窗口宽度
will be "0" for the NarrowLayout.
为0
(typing)
(打字中……)
And then we'll make this MinwindowWidth
然后我们设置宽布局的最小窗口宽度
"900" in the WideLayout.
为900
And remember this is really on a per app basis.
这种设置实际上基于于每个应用的设计
Whatever makes sense for your application,
只要在你的应用中合理
where the logical breaks are.
符合逻辑即可
So there's no like as I've said many times already,
就像我之间反复提及过的，
there's no standard way to do this that I'm aware of.
做这玩意没有一个标准的方法
I might be corrected as some point here, but...
这儿可能我需要修改一些地方，但是..
(typing)
(打字中……)
So we're going to set that MainPanel.Width,
我们设置 MainPanel.Width,
and let's make sure that we have
然后将它
that's called MainPanel here.
命名为MainPanel
Here I want to call this...
这里我想给它起个名字...
Give this Name...MainPanel.
就叫....MainPanel.
Okay? So we're going to set...
好了，我们还要
(typing on keyboard)
(打字中……)
(typing)
the MainPanel's Width to a value of 200.
把MainPanel的宽度设为200
(typing)
(打字中……)
And the MainPanel.Height
然后是MainPanel的高度
(typing)
(打字中……)
equal to 275.
等于275
Now keep in mind, this is just for (mumbles)
要记住，这些只是用于
the individual newsItems inside of our GridView.
我们Grid布局中每一个的newsItems
(takes a deep breath)
(深呼吸)
And then the other requirement was
然后其他的要求是
to...
去
(typing)
(打字中……)
set the...
设置
HeadlineTextBlock
Right?
对吧
(typing)
(打字中……)
.FontSize,
.FontSize (字体大小)
so the value equal to 18 there.
值设为18
Let me make sure I have that name set.
让我确认一下设置好了名字
Yeah, I do. HeadlineTextBlock. Great. Okay.
( •̀ ω •́ ) y   好的，没问题
HeadlineText, did I say box? That should be Block.
标题文体，刚刚我说了盒子吗？这应当是块
There we go.
让我们开始
Boy, it did not like that.
这不像刚刚那样
Oh.
噢
(typing)
(打字中……)
That'll be right, yeah. It just didn't like that.
这就好了，不像刚刚那样了
Okay, good alright, so then we'll change
好了，没问题了，然后我们要改变
each of these Setters up
这里面每一个Setter
when we go to the wide size.
当宽布局时
And so in this case we want 400 X 400,
我们想要设置为400*400
and...
然后
we'll set this Font at 26.
我们把字体设为26
(typing)
Great.
好
So that should complete the first of the two... items.
这样我们应该完成了这两个中的前一部分了
Now let's go over to the MainPage.xaml,
现在让我们跳转到MainPage.xaml
and we're going to need to add
我们需要去添加
a VisualStateManager.
一个视觉状态管理器
In fact, let me just do this.
这样吧
Because I hate typing all this stuff out.
因为我讨厌把这些东西都敲出来
Just grab all this, we'll strip out the stuff we don't need.
选择这些东西，然后去掉我们不需要的
(typing)
Alright, so we'll just get rid of these Setters,
好的，让我们去掉这些Setter
and I think the MinWindowWidth is going to be 400, any rate.
我认为这个最小窗口宽度应该是400，任何比例的
(sighing)
And so in this case what we're going to do
现在我们要做的是
is set the MyAutoSuggestBox.Visibility
设置 MyAutoSuggestBox 的可见性
and we'll set that equal to Collapsed.
我们把他设为Collapsed（收缩的）
(typing)
And then we'll do the same here,
然后在这里做同样的事情
(typing)
and it should be set to Visible,
它应该被设为Visible（可见的）
I believe is the property there.
我相信是这个属性
Alright. Let's save it, and let's see what we got.
好了，让我们保存一下，看看我们得到了什么
Alright, here goes nothing. Oh yeah, look at that.
好..这啥都没有,哦也♂，看啊
Font got bigger. The entire size of the item got larger.
字体变大了，整个元素都变大了♂
All right, now unfortunately
好吧，现在不幸的是
we can't really go smaller than 400.
我们不可以缩小到400
At least I can't, so to test this,
至少我不行，所以让我们来测试一下
what we're going to do...
我要做的是..
is change to the Mobile Emulator.
切换到手机模拟器
And test it there.
在这里测试
And ideally that SuggestBox will not be visible.
理论上，提示栏应该是看不见的
And you can see it is not visible.
你看，它是看不见的
I do have a little bit of... a little something
我还有一些其他的想法
I want to do up there with that TextBlock, up on top.
我想要对TextBlocks做一些改变
Let me play around with that real quick,
让我快速的查看一下其它东西
but other than that, I think we're pretty much done.
但是除此之外，我觉得已经做的差不多了
Yeah, I think it was too close to the top,
额，我想它太靠近顶部了
so all I wanna do
我现在要
is change the Margin a little bit.
稍稍改变一下边距的值
Push it down there and then
把它放下来，然后
let's see what the text...
看看文本是
That AutoSuggestBox, I'm going to have a closer eye
那个自动提示栏，我还要仔细看看它
at that too, cause I didn't pay attention to that.
因为我没有怎么去注意它
Alright, it does sit up a little high.
好了，把他在垫得高一点
I might push that down 5px.
我应该向下调整5px
So, push it down 5px.
向下5px
Yeah, I like that better.
好，我更喜欢这样
Okay, looks good.
嗯.看起来不错
Let me just make sure that there wasn't some other item.
让我确认一下没有其他的元素
Got that. Got that.
这个.这个都做到了
Got that. Did all that.
这也没问题了，都弄好了
Screenshots, got it, (mumbles) okay, NewsItem, got it.
截屏，好了，完事了
And I think we did all of that.
我认为我们做完了
For the most part, I think we're in good shape.
总体上，我觉得还不错
Okay, great, that's all there was to it.
好了，真棒，这是全部了
Hope you got it, or at least if you didn't get
希望你看懂了，或者你第一遍
it fist time around, that this helped you get unstuck.
没太理解，至少能教你怎么做
Alright, let's move on see you in the next video, thanks.
好了，让我们在下个视频见 谢谢 微软大法好